[{"answer": "What do you want me to do about it", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Take care of him", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Big is the key word, and Im telling you I want it bad", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Get rid of him", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I want you to get rid of Sailor", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes...  Get rid of him", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You need to explain it", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Simple?  Kill him?...  How", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Explain it...  I told you", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Shoot him?  Like with a gun", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Shoot Sailor in the head with a gun...  Now Im beginning to get it...  You want me to shoot Sailor in the head with a gun", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Are you going to provide me with an opportunity to prove my love to my girl?  Or are you gonna save youself some trouble and step up like a gentleman and apologize to her", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "This is a snakeskin jacket, and for me its a symbol of my individuality and my belief in personal freedom", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "...Thats an awful long way to go, just to get some pussy", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You still got plenty energy for me, baby", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Whatll it be like in that place, Sailor, do you think?  I hear it dont rain much there", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We got through two states already", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Gotta hex from a voodoo", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I wouldnt mind a little night life. How about you", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Maybe theres a place we could hear some music.  I feel like dancin. We could ask someone", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Honey, we bein strangers here and all, this is the kinda place we dont want to make nothin of nothin", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Im fine, mama.  I just wanted to tell you not to worry", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "If you mean Sailor, mama, yes I am", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Just a place", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Right?!  Mama, was it right for you to sic my friend on us?  How could you do that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Right?!  Mama, was it right for you to sic my friend on us?  How could you do that", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, mama, Im in that place, and were about to get on an airplane to that place", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend, I cant tell you, honey.  Is there anyway we can get on the road tonight?  Weve got to find them kids", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I did, honey, but that was last night...  Lets just find those two kids before its too late", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "...They was laughin arm in arm like animals", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " My mama...  So Sailor, our histories have been somewhat intertwined", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I didnt want to say it ... but I had a feelin my friend was up to somethin with your mama..", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "They have, sugar", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You heard right", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Life is unpredictable", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Be easy, Sailor.  Theres two employees. I take one in the back to open the safe, you keep the othern covered... You aint plannin on raisin a famly in Big Tuna, are ya", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Well...  I mean like my friend bein in a family way", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " I aint fuckin sure, my friend", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Have now", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Nice of you to drop by", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " You still screwing sixtee", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Wish Id fuckin cut you up good", "docId": "Wild-At-Heart.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "my friend called.  Theyre stayin another week", "qsentId": 46}]